President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of H. Patrick Swygert Records, 1977-1998; 13; 100 cubic ft.
  - Distinguished Service Professor Nominations, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Health and Safety, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Equipment Management, 1991-1992 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Ethics Commission Request, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Chancellor's Awards for Excellence, 1995-1996 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Excellence in Support Services, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Chancellor's Excellence Awards, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Excelsior School Task Force List, Undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Excelsior School, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Excelsior School, Undated (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - New Faculty/Staff, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Financial Aid, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Financial Aid, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Financial Management, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Golden Key National Honors Society, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Governor's Office, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Graduate Student Employees Union, Undated (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Student Organization, 1993-1995 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Greek Organizations, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Health Service, 1994-1995 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - ISAAC STERN Honorary Degree Nomination, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Honorary Degree, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Honorary Degree, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Honorary Degree, 1992 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Hudson Mohawk Association, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Hudson Mohawk Association, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Human Resource Management, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - IBM, Undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Information Systems & Technology, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Initiatives for women, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Arts in Education, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Arts in Education, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Health Care Management, 1994-1995 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Public Administration, 1994-1996 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Report of the President, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Report of the President, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Report of the President, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Realty Services-Opinion of Value, Undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Institute for Research on Women, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Institutional Research, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Institutional Services, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Internal Audit, 1993-1994 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Intersession, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Judicial System, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Inaugural Address: H. Patrick Swygert, Undated (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - King Commission, 1995 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - King Institute - Ella Baker Academy, 1992-1993 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - NYS Martin Luther King, Jr. Commission and Institute for Non Violence, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - King Memorial of Albany Inc., Undated (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Just Community, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Library, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Mailings, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Middle States Letter of Reaffirmation of Accreditation, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Middle States: Advisory Committee on Campus Priorities, Undated (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Military Recruiting, Undated (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - NASULGC, 1994 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - NY Council for the Humanities, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - NY Council for the Humanities Summer Teacher Institute, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - NYPIRG, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - NYS Black & Puerto Rican Caucus, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - NYS Department of Education, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - NYS Legislature, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - NYS Legislature re: Money Magazine, Undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - NYS Legislature, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - NYS Science/Technology Foundation, Undated (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - New York Theater Institute, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Office Hours, Open (HPS), Undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Organization Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Orientation, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Parking, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Paycheck Distribution Forms 10-91-Present, Undated (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Photographs - University at Albany, Undated (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Planning, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Presidential search, Undated (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Presidential Scholars, 1993-1994 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Presidential Scholars, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - President's Task Force on Women's Safety, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Public Safety, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program, Undated (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Purple and Gold, 1992-1994 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Racism, 1990-1991 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Reading Lists, Undated (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Recognition Dinner, 1993-1994 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - University Recruitment & Retention, 1993 August 31 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Enrollment- Admissions Principles, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Lowery Kathy - Discussion File, Undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Notes- HPS & Chancellor, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Open Meeting Hours, Undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - President's Report to University Senate, 1995 February 27 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Safety & Security Enhancement, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Sawchuk, Brown - Enrollment Marketing Study, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - University Center Presidents' Meeting, 1995 March 3 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Athletics, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Athletics - Gender Equity, Undated (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Athletics- Gender Equity- Folders 1,2,3, Undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Legal - Bowman, Archer, Undated (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - General Studies, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1993-1994; 1992 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Membership list, labels, phone numbers, Undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes, Undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, Undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Research Foundation, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Benchmark, 1990-1994 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Commission on Higher Education Annual Report of the Executive Director (1993-94)- 'Perspectives and Accomplishments', 1993-1994 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Budget Flexibility, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Economic Development Report Data, 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - IFR Policy, Undated (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Middle States (not accreditation), 1990-1994 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Commission on Higher Education (CHE); Middle States Association (MSA), Undated (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Native American Recruitment, 1992-1994 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - PEF/PSTP Summer/Fall1994 Tuition Support Voucher Program RFP, Undated (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Ron Hoskins' Information Presentation, Models of Organization, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Recruitment, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Sy Madanick, Undated (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Information Kiosks, Undated (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - (University) Recruitment and Retention Group, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Research Foundation, 1992-1994 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Research Foundation Initiative, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Residence Hall Occupancy, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI), 1992 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - (Discretionary) Salary Increases, 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Security Issues, 1992-1995 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Sesquicentennial - only contains 12/2/93 letter to University Community, 1993 December 2 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Space Management, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Speech Materials, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - State Education Department, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - (411 and 423)' State Street Property, 1989-1993 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Statistical Releases (SUNY Central IR), 1992-1994 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Strategic Planning, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Constituency Issues, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Enrollment - PEF RFP, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - (Public Service Training Program), Undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Enrollment Planning Principles, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Recruitment/Enrollment, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Recruitment/Retention Task Force, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Strategic Planning - Albany Public Schools, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Summer Planning Conference, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Summer Sessions, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - SUNY - Other Campuses, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - SUNY Central, Undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Survey on the University Economic Development, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - SUNY Day, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - SUNY Task Force on Economic Development (Norman Kurland report), 1992 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - SUNY 2000, Phase II, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - SUTRA (State University Tuition Reimbursable Account), 1993 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - (Supervising/Critic) Teacher Tuition Waiver Program, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - New York State Theatre Institute (NYSTI), 1991-1992 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Legislation Negotiated with Ways and Means, Undated (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Management Agreement, Undated (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Annual Fund, Undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Capital Campaign, Undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - African American Presidents of Higher Education, Undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Albany Student Press, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Florida, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Association, Undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - American Red Cross, Undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - American Red Cross, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Anti Defamation League, Undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Art and Mathematics Conference, Undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Authors & Editors, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Authors & Editors, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Barmaisers, Undated (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Benevolent Association, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Bill of Rights Program, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Brother to Brother, 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Budget Accounts, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Budget Planning, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Campus Center, Undated (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Campus Technology Initiatives, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Capital Campaign Video, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - CAS/ADA, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Center for Stress & Anxiety, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Center for the Study of Telecommunications, Undated (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - CESTM ~ Facility Branch Manager Search, Undated (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Undated (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Chapel House/Campus Ministry, Undated (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Collins, Evan R. (Memorial Service), Undated (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Collins Fellows, Undated (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Community College - Hudson Valley Community College, Undated (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Corporate Foundation Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Corporate Foundation Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Criminal Justice, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Education, School of Centers, Undated (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Education, Theory & Practice, 1991-1994 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Public administration, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Public Health Convocation, School of, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Registrar, 1993-1995 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Residential Life, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Senate - Presidential appointments, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Student Affairs, Vice President, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Tuition Teacher Tuition Waiver Program, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Tuition Teacher Tuition Waiver Program, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - UAS, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Initiative, Undated (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - United Way, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - University Foundation, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - University Foundation, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - University Foundation merger, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - University Foundation, Citizen Laureate Award, 1993-1996 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - University Relations, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Urban League, Undated (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - UUP, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - UUP, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Voices of Leadership, Undated (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Voices of Leadership II - Bios, Undated (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - WCDB, Undated (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - World Week, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - World Week, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Writers' Institute, Undated (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - African American Research Foundation, Undated (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Budget Policy & Priorities Committee, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Capital Facilities, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Chancellor's Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Chancellor Thomas Bartlett, Undated (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Construction Fund, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Construction Fund, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Contracts & Purchases, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Council of Presidents, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Distance Learning, President's Task Force on, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Doctoral Campus Presidents, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Educational Technology, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Educational Technology, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Employee Relations, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Employee Relations, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Senate, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Senate, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Finance and Business, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Finance and Business, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Government Relations, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Institutional Research, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Institutional Research, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - New York Office, Undated (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Provost, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Research Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Research Foundation, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Research Foundation, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Student Affairs & Special Programs, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Student Affairs & Special Programs, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Board of Trustees, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Campaign for Albany, Undated (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Commencement - Graduate Korb, Lawrence, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Williams, Juan, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Commencement, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Commencement, 1990-1991 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Diversity Conference, 1992-1994 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Recruitment - Letters from J. Gullahorn to Deans, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Fall Faculty Meeting, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Faculty-in-Residence Program, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Mentor Program, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Fuerza Latina (Student Activities), Undated (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - D. Bruce Johnstone Lecture, Undated (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Just Community, Undated (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Kerner Commission Symposium (Institute for Government), 1993 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - King Commission Annual Luncheon, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Minority Student Recruitment, Undated (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - New York Council for the Humanities Summer Teaching Institute, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Signum Laudis, Undated (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Small Business Development Center, Undated (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Student Association, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert-College of St. Rose Greetings, 1995 January 27 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Chancellor's Awards, 1995 February 10 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- CESTM- Community Forum Brief Overview of CESTM, 1995 February 15 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- University Senate President's Report, 1995 February 27 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- NYS Special Commission OpEd piece, 1994 January 14 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Tyron Residential 'Center/Hale Creek ASACT King: The Intellectual Activities for Justice, 1994 January 14 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Adirondack Comm. College Challenge & Change for the 1990s, 1994 January 20 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Sesquicentennialcentennial Opening Convocation Gwendolyn Brooks, 1994 January 27 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- NYS PTA, 1994 February 7 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Edith Tanenbaum Rudolf Room Dedication, 1994 February 17 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Community Forum Breakfast Overview CESTM, 1994 March 10 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Art Reception Welcome D. Byng, R. Callner, E. Cowley, 1994 March 12 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- SUNY Special Programs Institute, 1994 April 10 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Sesquicentennialcentennial Health Care Conference Insuring Success, 1994 April 18 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Health Care Conference Introduction - Governor Cuomo, 1994 April 19 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Report to the Faculty, 1994 May 4 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Rochester Urban League, 1994 May 10 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Commencement Address We Celebrate Ourselves, 1994 May 15 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- NY African American Research Foundation, 1994 May 20 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- American Jewish Congress Reflections on Campus Tensions, 1994 May 23 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Magnet School Observance of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Day, 1994 June 21 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Mitchel Livingston Farewell event, 1994 June 21 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Dr. Louis Vaccaro Forward to Vaccaro essays, 1994 August 11 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Rensselaerville Presbyterian Church Sermon, 1994 August 21 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- President's Report to the Faculty, 1994 September 13 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Friendship Baptist Church Retirement speech, 1994 October 15 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Small City School District Conference, 1994 October 17 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert-President H. Patrick Swygert-Rabbi Bernstein Society African-American Jewish Campus Communities Dialog or Division, 1994 October 23 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- October 26, 1994 Memorial Service for Tom Smith, 1994 October 26 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- October 27, 1994 SUNY Board of Trustees Academic Affairs Committee, 1994 October 27 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- November 4, 1994 Rev. Carl Tavlor's Retirement Keynote Address, 1994 November 4 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- November 19, 1994 Disabled High School Student Achievers, 1994 November 19 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- November 28, 1994 Senate Executive Committee President's Report, 1994 November 28 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- December 11, 1994 Phi Beta Kappa Initiation, 1994 December 11 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- December 21, 1994 Report to the Trustees "Safety', 1994 December 21 (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- January 7, 1993 NYU President's Roundtable National Press Club National Service Trust Fund, 1993 January 7 (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- January 15, 1993 Livingston Middle School King, Martin Luther, 1993 January 15 (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- January 26, 1993 Council for Humanities NYS Assembly Aid to Localities Budget Hearing, 1993 January 26 (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- February18, 1993 Unlimited Minds Reception Where Do We Go From Here, 1993 February 18 (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- February 22, 1993 NYS Dept. Motor Vehicles Keynote - One Nation-Many People: Strength in Diversity, 1993 February 22 (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- March 24, 1993 Golden Key Ceremony Induction Keynote Address, 1993 March 24 (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- April 22, 1993 Diversity Enrichment Institute Sage College One Nation--Many People: Strength in Diversity, 1993 April 22 (Box 82, Folder 42)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- May 5, 1993 Univ. at Albany Remarks to the Faculty, 1993 May 5 (Box 82, Folder 43)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- May 11, 1993 Dean's Reception, 1993 May 11 (Box 82, Folder 44)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- May 19, 1993 Hudson Mohawk Annual Dinner Remarks, 1993 May 19 (Box 82, Folder 45)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- May 20, 1993 Urban League Annual Dinner Building on our Strength for the 21st Century, 1993 May 20 (Box 82, Folder 46)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- May 23, 1993 Fulton-Montgomery Comm. College Changes and Challenges - College Commencement Address, 1993 May 23 (Box 82, Folder 47)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- June 6, 1993 St. Peter's Church One Nation-Many People: Strength in Diversity, 1993 June 6 (Box 82, Folder 48)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- June 24, 1993 Regents' College Graduation, 1993 June 24 (Box 82, Folder 49)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- Ju1y 19, 1993 Humanities Teachers' Institute, 1993 July 19 (Box 82, Folder 50)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- September 14, 1993 Remarks to the Faculty, 1993 September 14 (Box 82, Folder 51)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- October 1, 1993' Hudson Valley Comm. College 40th Anniversary Gala, 1993 September 14 (Box 82, Folder 52)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- October 15, 1993 NYS School Board Assoc., 1993 October 15 (Box 82, Folder 53)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- October 20, 1993 Authors & Editors, 1993 May 20 (Box 82, Folder 54)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- October 25, 1993 Unveiling Collins Fellows Portrait, 1993 October 25 (Box 82, Folder 55)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- October 26, 1993 Inauguration of College of Arts & Sciences, 1993 October 26 (Box 82, Folder 56)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- November 10, 1993 State Author/State Poet Ceremony, 1993 November 10 (Box 82, Folder 57)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- November 28, 1993 Mt. Calvary Baptist Church, 1993 November 28 (Box 82, Folder 58)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- November 30, 1993 Introduction of Ernest Boyer, 1993 November 30 (Box 82, Folder 59)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- November 30, 1993 William Henry Hastie Lecture, 1993 November 30 (Box 82, Folder 60)
  - Speeches - President H. Patrick Swygert- November 1993 History 328 Lawyers in American Life, 1993 November (Box 82, Folder 61)